this Sunday is Super Bowl
51 and as your friends with broken
kneecaps will tell you you can place
bets on absolutely everything uh way
more than just whether or not bill bich
will masturbate through his hoodie
Pockets
uh some of the real prop bets you can
make uh actually make on Super Bowl
Sunday include 25 to1 odds someone
catches fire during the Lady Gaga
halftime show and 45 to1 odds a fan
throws a d on the field and if you're
wondering how a fan would get access to
a dildo let me repeat Lady Gaga halftime
show so comedians the possibilities are
endless please come up with as many more
prop bets for the Super Bowl as you can
in 60 seconds and begin Kenner uh 50 to
one odds at Chris Hardwick spend Super
Bowl Sunday watching reruns of Star Trek
next Generation yeah very it's very
likely very likely you don't know could
be could be Doctor Who you don't know or
stranger things uh Ashling uh 10 to one
odds that the Russians already know who
won the Super Bowl yeah
points one to one odds that Trump will
tweet that his crowds were bigger yeah
points actually 50 to one odds on
record-breaking attendance at AA
meetings on Super Bowl Monday yes
point one to one odds that a guy wearing
a make America great again hat will come
in his pants when he sees the word
Patriot all right
[Applause]
point